Hadi Gunawan

hadigunawan987@gmail.com | +6285781722743 | South Tangerang, Banten 15224 | linkedin.com/in/hadi-gunawan-875889199/

SUMMARY

Hello, my name is Hadi Gunawan and I am a fresh graduate from University of Pamulang majoring Informatics Engineering, I have work experience for approximately 2 years. Tech-savvy, I have enthusiasm to have a career in the data field for instance: Data Analyst, Data Scientist etc, but do not rule out opportunities in other fields. Eager to learn and adapt to a new technology tools or method used.

EXPERIENCE

Retention and Winback, Myrepublic ID

Aug 2018 - July 2020

- Make outbound call to costumers who have a disconected status of subscription in order to minimize the occurrence of churn, using customer data from CRM (customer and target oriented)
- Escalated reports related to customer problem and rewards to customers. Using google sheets,
 CRM and tools for instance: Zendesk, internal CRM
- Communicate with other co-worker with same or in another division to achieve target goals

Data Entry Assistant Intern, BP2T South Tangerang

Jan 2016 - Feb 2016

- Entry data into Microsoft Excel
- Organizing a pysical data into the warehouse and maintaining them

LICENSE AND CERTIFICATIONS

SQL Fundamentals Skill Track (DataCamp)

Learning and practicing about Structured Query Language (SQL), in this course I learning from basic to intermediate, window function, correlated queries, nested queries, Common Table Expressions (CTE), built-in PostgreSQL functions and many more

Learning Data Analytics (Roadmap by LinkedIn Course)

Learning about data analyst role including soft skills and hard skills such as data cleaning, data manipulation and data visualization using power bi and Ms. excel

Tableau Fundamentals Skill Track (DataCamp)

Learning and practicing about data preparation, identification, data visualization, insight, dashboard, story using tableau. And many more online course

SKILLS

Hard Skills and Tools: Visual Studio Code, Excel, Word, PowerPoint, SQL, Tableau, Power Bi, Google Sheets, Google Data Studio, HTML, CSS, Github, MySQL, Adobe Photoshop, (Novice: SQL Server, PHP, Python, Flutter, AWS)

Soft Skills: Communication, Critical Thinking, Teamwork, Adaptability, Prosedural Thinking

EDUCATION

University of Pamulang

Sept 2017 – Aug 2021

GPA: 3.46

Bachelor of Informatic Engineering

Relevant coursework: Database, Algorithms and Programming, Data Communication, Statistics, Informatics Logic, Calculus, Basic Physics, Computer Programming, Data Structures, AI, DSS.